# DAVID DESCHENEAUX

734 546 2431



desch@protonmail.com



2805 Green Valley Dr. Ann Arbor, MI 48103

## EDUCATION

DEV BOOTCAMP Apprentice 2014-2015

19-week intensive boot camp focusing on Ruby on Rails and JavaScript.

EASTERN MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY Political Science 2010-2013

Statistical & Public Policy Analysis

## SKILLS

Communication

**Understanding Client Needs** 

Maintaining Relationships

Sales

Microsoft Office

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Strong Written & Verbal Skills

HODL'er

#### AWARDS

DEAN'S LIST Eastern Michigan University 2012

PI SIGMA ALPHA National Political Science Honor Society

#### PROFILE

I'm a talented and enthusiastic worker looking to pivot into a space that I believe will change the world for the better. I have great interpersonal skills and I relish in opportunities to share my knowledge and expertise for those that have questions. I've been into Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies since 2017 and I've spent a majority of my free time researching and learning as much as I possibly can about the topic. I now aim to translate that knowledge and passion into employment in what I believe is the most profound and important paradigm shift the world has seen in generations.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **NOBU MALIBU**

SERVER | June 2014 - November 2020

As one of the most high profile and world-renowned restaurants in the world, it was my job to leave all guests satisfied with exemplary service that consistently exceeded expectations of our high profile and discerning clientele.

- Problem solving under duress.
- Maintaining relationships and confidentiality
- Understanding guest's needs
- Excellent communication
- High Volume Sales

## LOW FREQUENCY MANAGEMENT

MANAGER | 2007 - 2014

- Managed and staffed multiple venues throughout the metro Detroit area.
- Planned and facilitated nightclub events for up to 1000 guests.

### NORTHWESTERN MUTUAL

## RESEARCH ASSISTANT | 2009 - 2010

- Implemented existing market research for client presentations.
- Researched and analyzed data for existing and potential clients.